<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grant County Economic Development</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Grant County Economic Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Grant County Economic Development</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of AI in Art</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-rise-of-ai-in-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/the-rise-of-ai-in-art/</guid>
      <description>Recently AI has exploded and been used for everything from writing poetry to drawing portraits and even creating music for musicians. AI has taken off in two major creative areas, writing, and art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots Trellis on the WSL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/installing-trellis-on-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/installing-trellis-on-wsl/</guid>
      <description>I’ve used Roots Trellis for a long time. When I first started using it I was designing and developing on a MacBook Pro. Developing on Apple products is a dream come true. It’s a fantastic environoment for development, and using libraries like Node.js.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting Your Website for Free</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/host-your-website-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/host-your-website-for-free/</guid>
      <description>When starting as a web developer, it can be hard to know where to host your site. If you want the most robust platform with the most flexibility, then deploying a server on DigitalOcean is likely your best bet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OctoMob</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/octomob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/octomob/</guid>
      <description>OctoMob is an NFT (Non-Fungible Token) project for which I created the art on the Ethereum Blockchain. The first collection was a hand-drawn collection of 99 custom-made NFTs, sold at auction and individually on the Ethereum Blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Grant County Economic Development is about creating and helping people. That&amp;rsquo;s why I decided to start my own business—to help others looking for an online presence, digital marketing, branding, and illustration. My goal is to provide customers with high-quality artwork, websites, social media artwork, videos, and animations that will help them build an audience and engage with brands visually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description> Got a technical issue? Want to send feedback, or would you like to get started on a project? Need details about a Business plan, or a proposal? Let me know.
Your Name: (Required) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>At Grant County Economic Development, accessible from https://ugranted.org, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Grant County Economic Development and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Grant County Economic Development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Grant County Economic Development!
These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of Grant County Economic Development&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at https://ugranted.org.
By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use Grant County Economic Development if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.
The following terminology applies to these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement and Disclaimer Notice and all Agreements: &amp;ldquo;Client&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Your&amp;rdquo; refers to you, the person log on this website and compliant to the Company’s terms and conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for signing up for the newsletter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email-thank-you/</guid>
      <description> I appreicate you taking the time to signup for my newsletter. Get notififed when new articles and posts are published. Unsubscribe at any time.
Back to Homepage </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact-thank-you/</guid>
      <description> I appreicate you taking the time to contact me. I will get back to you ASAP. My usual response time is a few hours, but rest assured, I will contact you in 48 hours or less.
Back to Homepage </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools of the Trade</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tools/</guid>
      <description>These are the tools and gadgets, that make me a Swiss Army Knife. I often get asked about the tools, apps, and services I use to succeed in my work. Here’s a list of my favorite tools that I use daily. They’ve helped me build a successful business and would also be a great addition to anyone’s arsenal.
Work Station AMD 5950X Custom, 128GB RAM, with an Nvidia 3090 Ti Ultra I use an AMD 5950X with 128GB DDR4 3600 Corsair Vengeance for my workstation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/web/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boy In the Corner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/boy-in-the-corner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/boy-in-the-corner/</guid>
      <description>When I was contacted by Boy in the Corner Studios A.K.A the “Toy Assassin” Heath Duntz, and I was ecstatic. I&amp;rsquo;ve been collecting custom made toys for years, but honestly… I had a hard time containing my excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flint Oak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/flint-oak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/flint-oak/</guid>
      <description>I really did try to push for a concept and the 5 star showing the end of shells turned out fantastic. It never did get printed or ran, but I kept this project, because it showcases great art and copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper Mower</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>Nothing says industrial design like mowers, eh? I did a lot of work for Grasshopper, print, web, digital, and trade show collateral. All I can say is that if you ever drive one of these things, you&amp;rsquo;ll ever want to look at a push mower again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyspeco Inc.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/hyspeco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/hyspeco/</guid>
      <description>Hyspeco is a Parker Hannifin distributor for hydraulics, pneumatics, industrial hose and fittings, industrial tools, industrial lifting equipment, and custom-designed engineering solutions. Hyspecos stocked inventory includes a wide selection of hydraulic products, including cylinders, valves, pumps, motors, and components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mears Inc.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/mears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/mears/</guid>
      <description>I help companies small and large build brands. Some are a branded houses, but Mears is a House of Brands. They package fertilizer, and ice-melt for companies of all different sizes. So I&amp;rsquo;ve helped them with not only their company branding and identity, I&amp;rsquo;ve also helped them create many brands that are specific to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Continent Instruments and Avionics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/mcico/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/mcico/</guid>
      <description>Mid-Continent Instruments and Avionics has been an industry leader in the overhaul, exchange, repair, design, and manufacturing of aircraft instruments, avionics, and advanced power solutions for over half a century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Kansas Ear, Nose &amp; Throat</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/wss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/wss/</guid>
      <description>I really did try to push for a concept and the 5 star showing the end of shells turned out fantastic. It never did get printed or ran, but I kept this project, because it showcases great art and copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flying Stove</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/flying-stove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/flying-stove/</guid>
      <description>For the last few years food trucks have been all the rage. The Schauf brothers contacted me about branding their food truck. Jeff had been living in California for the last few years&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wesley Medical Center</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/wesley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/wesley/</guid>
      <description>I worked on the campaign “Intensive Caring” for Wesley Medical Center. The print campaign coordinated :30 second tv spots followed by a print campaign that was ran in various media outlets throughout the area. I worked with a talented group of individuals, and we won a Silver Addy for our efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
