<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logo Design on Grant County Economic Development</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/logo-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logo Design on Grant County Economic Development</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Grant County Economic Development</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:10:36 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/logo-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OctoMob</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/octomob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/octomob/</guid>
      <description>OctoMob is an NFT (Non-Fungible Token) project for which I created the art on the Ethereum Blockchain. The first collection was a hand-drawn collection of 99 custom-made NFTs, sold at auction and individually on the Ethereum Blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boy In the Corner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/boy-in-the-corner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/boy-in-the-corner/</guid>
      <description>When I was contacted by Boy in the Corner Studios A.K.A the “Toy Assassin” Heath Duntz, and I was ecstatic. I&amp;rsquo;ve been collecting custom made toys for years, but honestly… I had a hard time containing my excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flint Oak</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/flint-oak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/flint-oak/</guid>
      <description>I really did try to push for a concept and the 5 star showing the end of shells turned out fantastic. It never did get printed or ran, but I kept this project, because it showcases great art and copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper Mower</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>Nothing says industrial design like mowers, eh? I did a lot of work for Grasshopper, print, web, digital, and trade show collateral. All I can say is that if you ever drive one of these things, you&amp;rsquo;ll ever want to look at a push mower again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mears Inc.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/mears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/mears/</guid>
      <description>I help companies small and large build brands. Some are a branded houses, but Mears is a House of Brands. They package fertilizer, and ice-melt for companies of all different sizes. So I&amp;rsquo;ve helped them with not only their company branding and identity, I&amp;rsquo;ve also helped them create many brands that are specific to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Continent Instruments and Avionics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/mcico/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/mcico/</guid>
      <description>Mid-Continent Instruments and Avionics has been an industry leader in the overhaul, exchange, repair, design, and manufacturing of aircraft instruments, avionics, and advanced power solutions for over half a century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flying Stove</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/flying-stove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 11:10:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/flying-stove/</guid>
      <description>For the last few years food trucks have been all the rage. The Schauf brothers contacted me about branding their food truck. Jeff had been living in California for the last few years&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
